Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Annotated Scores, 1828-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Unmarked scores, 1801-1992, II.; Folder 608-Folder 876
  - Gershwin, George, 1898-1937 Rialto ripples (Rag), 1917, 1 score (2 pages); Print (photocopy) New World Music Instrumentation: For solo piano Additional name: Donaldson, Will, 1891-1954 (Box 30, Folder 0689)
  - Ginastera, Alberto, 1916-1983 Sonata no. 2: for piano, op. 53, 1981, 1 score (25 pages); Print Boosey & Hawkes Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 30, Folder 0690)
  - Ginastera, Alberto, 1916-1983 Toccata: piano solo, 1973, 1 score (10 pages); Print Boosey & Hawkes Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. Originally a toccata for organ by Domenico Zipoli. Additional name: Zipoli, Domenico, 1688-1726 (Box 30, Folder 0691)
  - Glanville-Hicks, Peggy Obeisance to a Lucite spectrum, 1949, 1 score (1 page); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Transcribed by Mikhashoff; on verso is photocopy of holograph version. For John Cage, on his birthday, Sept. 5, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 0692)
  - Godowsky, Leopold, 1870-1938 Renaissance. Elegie, 1906, 1 score (7 pages); Print Schlesinger'sche Buch und Musikhandlung Instrumentation: For solo piano Based on the Elegie by Jean Philipp Rameau. Band 1 no. 5 of Renaissance, freie Bearbeitungen alter Meisterstücke. Additional name: Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764 (Box 30, Folder 0693)
  - Godowsky, Leopold, 1870-1938 Renaissance. Tambourin, 1906, 1 score (7 pages); Print Schlesinger'sche Buch und Musikhandlung Instrumentation: For solo piano Based on the Tambourin by Jean Philipp Rameau. Band 1 no. 6 of Renaissance, freie Bearbeitungen alter Meisterstücke. Additional name: Rameau, Jean-Philippe, 1683-1764 (Box 30, Folder 0694)
  - Godowsky, Leopold, 1870-1938 Renaissance. Minuet, E flat major, 1906, 1 score (6 pages); Print Schlesinger'sche Buch und Musikhandlung Instrumentation: For solo piano Missing last page. Based on Johann Schobert's Minuet in E-flat major. Band 2 no. 7 of Renaissance, freie Bearbeitungen alter Meisterstücke. Additional name: Schobert, Johann, -1767 (Box 30, Folder 0695)
  - Godowsky, Leopold, 1870-1938 Renaissance. Pastorale, 1906, 1 score (4 pages); Print Schlesinger'sche Buch und Musikhandlung Instrumentation: For solo piano Jacket missing, 3-6 p. Based on Arcangelo Corelli's Pastorale in G major. Band 2 no. 8 of Renaissance, freie Bearbeitungen alter Meisterstücke. Additional name: Corelli, Arcangelo, 1653-1713 (Box 30, Folder 0696)
  - Godowsky, Leopold, 1870-1938 Renaissance. Sarabande, E minor, 1906, 2 score (5 pages each); Print Schlesinger'sche Buch und Musikhandlung Instrumentation: For solo piano Based on Jean Baptiste Lully's Sarabande in E minor. Band 2 no. 9 of Renaissance, freie Bearbeitungen alter Meisterstücke. Additional name: Lully, Jean Baptiste, 1632-1687 (Box 30, Folder 0697)
  - Godowsky, Leopold, 1870-1938 Renaissance. Caquet, 1906, 2 scores (6 and 9 pages); Print Schlesinger'sche Buch und Musikhandlung Instrumentation: For solo piano Based on Jean François Dandrieu's Le caquet and Jean-Baptiste Loeilly's Gigue in E major. Band 2 no. 11-12 of Renaissance, freie Bearbeitungen alter Meisterstücke. Additional name: Dandrieu, Jean François, 1682-1738; Lœillet, J. B. (Jean-Baptiste), 1653-1728 (Box 30, Folder 0698)
  - Goehr, Alexander, 1932- Capriccio: for piano, op. 6, 1959, 1 score (6 pages); Print B. Schott's Söhne Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 30, Folder 0699)
  - Golub, Peter, 1952- Malady of Harlequin: nine piano pieces, 1982, 1 score (15 pages); Holograph (ozalid copy) American Composers Alliance Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 30, Folder 0700)
  - Granados, Enrique, 1867-1916 Goyescas. Quejas, undated, 1 score (5 pages); Print (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 30, Folder 0701)
  - Grant, Joyce, 1937- Reflections (of the 60's) for piano, violin, voice and percussion, 1984, 4 scores (6 pages each); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For piano, violin, voice, and percussion One copy signed by the composer and with performance markings. Dedicated to Mikhashoff. (Box 30, Folder 0702)
  - Grieg, Edvard, 1843-1907 Norske folkeviser og danse. Selections, undated, 1 score (5 pages; Print (photocopy) C. F. Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 30, Folder 0703)
    13. Reiselied -- 18. Stabbe-Laaten: (humoristischer Tanz) -- 19. Hølje Dale -- 23. Bauernlied -- 24. Brautlied -- 25. Rabenhochzeit.
  - Griffes, Charles Tomlinson, 1884-1920 Three preludes: piano solo, 1967, 1 score (7 pages); Print C. F. Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 30, Folder 0704)
  - Gruenberg, Louis, 1884-1964 Emperor Jones. Selections, 1932, 1 score (13 pages); Print (photocopy) Cos-Cob Press Instrumentation: Vocal score Found in a folder labeled Around the World with American Opera. (Box 30, Folder 0705)
  - Gruenberg, Louis, 1884-1964 Jazz Masks. Selections, undated, 1 score (17 pages); Print (photocopy) Universal Edition Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 30, Folder 0706)
    Spring song (Mendelssohn) (5 pages) -- Barcarolle (Offenbach) (7 pages) -- Melody in F (Rubinstein) (5 pages)
  - Gudmundsen-Holmgreen, Pelle Udstillingsbilleder, 1972, 1 score (13 pages); Print Wilhelm Hansen Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 30, Folder 0707)
  - Hageman, Richard, 1882-1966 Caponsacchi. Selections, 1931, 1 score (20 pages); Print (photocopy) Adler Instrumentation: Vocal score of opera Photocopy of vocal score, found in a folder labeled “Around the World with American Opera.” First 20 pages of opera. (Box 30, Folder 0708)
  - Von Hagen, P. A. (Peter Albrecht), -1837 Will not dare not tell: a new song written by Mrs. Rowson, 1801, 1 score (2 pages); Print (photocopy) P. A. von Hagen Instrumentation: For voice and piano with optional flute Additional name: Rowson, Mrs., 1762-1824 (Box 30, Folder 0709)
  - Hanaoka, Katsunori Tolegorit, undated, 1 score (22 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Composer's notes on the compositions on versos of title sheets. (Box 30, Folder 0710)
  - Hans, W. Klavierstücke, 1986, 1 score (10 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Dedicated to Wolfgang Heyer. Three works. Title and name in caption not clear. (Box 30, Folder 0711)
  - Harris, Edward, b. 1899 Chopin in the citrus belt: a nocturne for the left hand and an orange, 1938, 1 score (5 pages); Print C. Fischer Instrumentation: For solo piano Very fragile condition. (Box 30, Folder 0712)
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Summerfield set, 1988, 1 score( 10 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano or harpsichord Accompanied by second photocopy. There is typescript text from De rerum natura by Lucretius in the caption: For you alone can bless mankind with tranquil peace …" (Box 30, Folder 0713)
    Sonata -- Air -- Ground -- Round for the triumph of Alexander.
  - Hartley, Walter S. (Walter Sinclair), 1927- Three preludes, for piano (1976-7), 1977, 1 score (7 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 31, Folder 0714)
  - Harvey, Jonathan, 1939- Four images after Yeats: for piano solo, 1984, 1 score (33 pages); Print Novello Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 31, Folder 0715)
  - Hawley, William, 1950- Fantasy for piano, 1982, 1 score (5 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 31, Folder 0716)
  - Heinrich, Anthony Philip, 1781-1861 Dawning of music in Kentucky. Selections, 1820, 1 score (4 pages); Print (photocopy) Bacon & Hart Instrumentation: For voice and piano (Box 31, Folder 0717)
    How sleep the brave -- The bride's farewell
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Children's suite for piano, 1949, 1 score (16 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 31, Folder 0718)
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Machine music, 1967, 1 score (28 pages); Print T. Presser Instrumentation: Piano, percussion and two-channel tape recorder Signed by Jan Williams. Missing pages 1-7 (Box 31, Folder 0719)
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Six easy pieces: for violin and piano (1974), 1981, 1 score (12 pages); Print Instrumentation: For violin and piano (Box 31, Folder 0720)
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Sonata no. 5: for piano (1961), 1973, 1 score (38 pages); Print C. F. Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano The print publication was edited and fingered by Yvar Mikhashoff. (Box 31, Folder 0721)
  - Ives, Charles, 1874-1954 Largo, undated, 1 score (4 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For violin, clarinet, and piano Found in folder marked Charles Ives; Drawer #1. 2 copies of each page (to get the full width of the entire page). (Box 31, Folder 0722)
  - Ives, Charles, 1874-1954 Lecture: Tolerance, undated, 1 part; Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For flute, clarinet, 2 bassoons, snare drum, and strings Arranged by Gunther Schuller. From Set no. 1. Single, treble clef part, probably for clarinet. Additional name: Schuller, Gunther (Box 31, Folder 0723)
  - Ives, Charles, 1874-1954 New River, undated, 1 score (4 pages); Print (photocopy) Instrumentation: For chorus, piano, piccolo/flute, 2 clarinets, baritone saxophone, 2 trumpets, trombone, strings, and timpani Full score created from cutting and pasting all the parts on a single page. Original taped together copy, and photocopy. (Box 31, Folder 0724)
  - Ives, Charles, 1874-1954 New River, undated, 3 parts on 2 leaves; Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For chorus, piano, and instrumental ensemble Edited by Gunther Schuller. Additional name: Schuller, Gunther (Box 31, Folder 0725)
  - Ives, Charles, 1874-1954 Pond, 1973, 1 score (7 pages); Print Boelke-Bomart Instrumentation: For voice, flute, 2 harps or celesta, piano and string orchestra Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 31, Folder 0726)
  - Jack, Adrian, 1943- For orchestra with piano (1973), 1978, 1 score (35 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For orchestra and piano (Box 31, Folder 0727)
  - Jaggard, David Piano music. Selections, undated, 23 pages; Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Includes a photocopy of Peggy Glanville-Hicks solo piano work, Obeisance to a lucite spectrum. Additional name: Glanville-Hicks, Peggy (Box 31, Folder 0728)
    Works include: Brown (2 copies), Stupid (2 copies), Move (2 copies), 2 untitled pieces.
  - Janssen, Guus, 1951- Keer: for orchestra, 1989, 1 score (63 pages); Manuscript (reproduction) Donemus Instrumentation: For orchestra Spiral bound. (Box 31, Folder 0729)
  - Johnson, D. Passion artist, undated, 1 score (11 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For two pianos (Box 31, Folder 0730)
  - Kendall, James In paradisum, undated, 2 scores (1 page each); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For soprano, alto, and tenor voices Gregorian chant arranged by Kendall. One score is in open format, the other is closed format. (Box 31, Folder 0731)
  - King, John, 1953 Nov. 28- Tangovariations, 1984, 1 score (41 pages); Manuscript (Photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 31, Folder 0732)
  - Kirkpatrick, William Chaise Musicales, undated, 2 pages; Print (photocopy) Instrumentation: For musicians, speaker, and dancer Photocopy of typed performance instructions. Also includes printed concert program for March 8, 1978 performance. (Box 31, Folder 0733)
  - Knox, Doug Theme and variations for harpsichord, undated, 1 score (12 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo harpsichord "To Barbara Harbach". (Box 31, Folder 0734)
  - Kohlsaat, Caroline, 1875- Bread and roses, undated, 1 score (1 page); Print (photocopy) Instrumentation: For voice and piano Originally inserted with Christian Wolff's Bread and roses which is based on the song. Words by James Oppenheim. Additional name: Oppenheim, James, 1882-1932 (Box 31, Folder 0735)
  - Kondo, Jo, 1947- Sight rhythmics: piano, 1980, 1 score (9 pages); Print (reproduction of manuscript) C. F. Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 31, Folder 0736)
  - Korn, Peter Jona Piano sonata no. 1, 1957, 1 score (20 pages); Print Boosey & Hawkes Instrumentation: For solo piano Stamped R. MacKay. (Box 31, Folder 0737)
  - Kubik, Gail, 1914- Sonata for piano, 1950, 1 score (40 pages); Print Southern Music Instrumentation: For solo piano Edited by Frank Glazer. Additional name: Glazer, Frank (Box 31, Folder 0738)
  - Lanier, Sidney, 1842-1881 Blackbirds: for solo flute (and accompaniment), undated, 1 score (12 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For flute and piano (Box 31, Folder 0739)
  - Lavista, Mario, 1943- Pieza para un(a) pianista y un piano, 1972, 1 score (4 pages); Print (photocopy) Ediciones Mexicanas de Musica Instrumentation: For solo piano Enlarged photocopy, taped together. (Box 31, Folder 0740)
  - Lees, Benjamin, 1924-2010 Sonata breve, 1959, 1 score (24 pages); Print Boosey & Hawkes Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 31, Folder 0741)
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Angelus!: Priere aux Anges gardiens, undated, 4 parts; Print (photocopy) B. Schott's Sohne Instrumentation: For 2 violins, viola, and violoncello (Box 32, Folder 0742)
    Found in folder marked Liszt Chamber Works. Parts for Violin 1 & 2, Viola, and Violoncello.
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Années de pèlerinage III, no. 4: Les jeux deau a la villa d'este, 1949, 1 score (20 pages); Print Salabert Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff and dated June 1, 1981, Paris. Edited by Alfred Cortot. Additional name: Cortot, Alfred, 1877-1962 (Box 32, Folder 0743)
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Bevezctes es magyar Indulo = Introduction and Hungarian march, undated, 1 score (17 pages); Print (photocopy) Lipcse Instrumentation: For solo piano Spiral bound. Edited by Imretol Szechenyi. Additional name: Szechenyi, Imretol (Box 32, Folder 0744)
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Deux legendes, 1949, 1 score (39 pages); Print Salabert Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff and dated June 1, 1981, Paris. Edited by Alfred Cortot. Additional name: Cortot, Alfred, 1877-1962 (Box 32, Folder 0745)
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Élégie, 1828, 1 score (11 pages) and 3 parts; Print (photocopy) C. F. Kahnt Instrumentation: For violoncello, piano, harp, and harmonium Found in folder marked Liszt Chamber Works. (Box 32, Folder 0746)
    Photocopies, three parts, two copies of the score
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Fantaisie sur Szep Ilonka de Mosonyi, 1868, 1 score (11 pages); Print (photocopy) Rózsavölgyi & Co. Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 32, Folder 0747)
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 11ème Rhapsodies hongroise, 1949, 1 score (16 pages); Print Salabert Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff and dated July 27, 1967. Edited by Alfred Cortot. Additional name: Cortot, Alfred, 1877-1962 (Box 32, Folder 0748)
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Rhapsodies hongroises IX: Carnaval de Pesth, undated, 1 score (21 pages) and 2 parts; Print (photocopy) B. Schott's Söhne Instrumentation: For violin, violoncello, and piano; originally for solo piano Found in folder marked “Liszt Chamber Works” Spiral bound photocopies of printed score and 2 parts. (Box 32, Folder 0749)
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Trauer-Gondel Nr. 1, undated, 1 score (3 pages); Print (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 32, Folder 0750)
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Pieces, piano, no. 1, A-flat major, 1935, 1 score (2 pages); Print (photocopy) Evans Bros. Instrumentation: For solo piano Titled An unpublished Liszt manuscript in The piano student, Dec. 1935, pages 64-65. A manuscript then in the possession of Rev. Greville Cooke. (Box 32, Folder 0751)
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Zelle in Nonnenwerth: Élégie, 1883, 1 score (4 pages); Print (photocopy) P. J. Tanger's Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 32, Folder 0752)
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Short sonata for piano no. 2, 1976, 1 score (9 pages); Print Joshua Corporation Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 32, Folder 0753)
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Short sonata for piano no. 3, 1976, 1 score ( 11 pages); Print Joshua Corporation Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 32, Folder 0754)
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Short sonata for piano no. 4, 1976, 1 score (12 pages); Print Joshua Corporation Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 32, Folder 0755)
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Short sonata for piano no. 5, 1981, 1 score (8 pages); Print Joshua Corporation Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 32, Folder 0756)
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Short sonata for piano no. 6, 1981, 1 score ( 8 pages); Print Joshua Corporation Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 32, Folder 0757)
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Song without words for piano, undated, 1 score (4 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Dedicated to Mikhashoff. (Box 32, Folder 0758)
  - Lutyens, Elisabeth, 1906-1983 Piano e forte, 1965, 1 score (13 pages); Print (photocopy) Mills Music Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 32, Folder 0759)
  - Maderna, Bruno Serenata per un satellite, 1970, 1 score (2 pages); Print Ricordi Instrumentation: For violin, flute/piccolo, oboe/oboe d'amore/musette, clarinet, marimba, harp, guitar, and mandolin, performed together or separately. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 32, Folder 0760)
  - Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911 Klavierquartett (1876), 1973, 1 score (30 pages) and 3 parts; Print Hans Sikorski Instrumentation: For piano, violin, viola, and violoncello Signed by Mikhashoff and dated Aug. 9, 1988 Darmstadt. (Box 32, Folder 0761)
  - Maslíah, Leo 5 Piezas Cortas, undated, 1 score (4 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Found in folder marked Argentina and Uruguay Piano Music. (Box 32, Folder 0762)
  - Mason, Benedict, 1954- Piano sonata, undated, 1 score (8 pages); Holograph (Photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 32, Folder 0763)
  - McCandless, Michael, 1957-1993 Another felicitude [incomplete], undated, 1 score (5 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For violin, marimba, piano, and contrabass. Note from the composer to Mikhashoff on score. Incomplete. (Box 32, Folder 0764)
  - Merril, Todd Post-Rondo with optional programmatic subtitle ... or How I spent my summer vacation, 1992, 1 score ( 3 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 32, Folder 0765)
  - Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993 Dances for Davia: first set, 1981, 1 score (23 pages); Print Southern Music Instrumentation: For flute and piano Signed by Mikhashoff. Two copies. (Box 32, Folder 0766)
  - Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974 Album de Madame Bovary: 17 short pieces for piano, 1934, 1 score (12 pages); Print Enoch Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 32, Folder 0767)
  - Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974 Concertino d'automne: pour deux pianos et huit instruments, 1952, 1 score (69 pages); Print Heugel Instrumentation: For 2 pianos and 8 instruments Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 32, Folder 0768)
  - Chesimò, 1908-1992 Ala spaziole: aerosintesi, undated, 1 score (1 page); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Mario Monachesi used the name Chesimò. Found in folder marked “Italian Futurist Music.” (Box 32, Folder 0769)
  - Chesimò, 1908-1992 Scarica elettrica, undated, 1 scoure (1 page); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Mario Monachesi used the name Chesimò. Found in folder marked Italian Futurist Music (Box 32, Folder 0770)
  - Montague, Stephen Paramell V for 2 pianos, 1983, 1 score (12 pages); Manuscript (facsimile) United music Instrumentation: For 2 pianos Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 32, Folder 0771)
  - Montague, Stephen Paramell Va: for piano solo, 1984, 1 score (7 pages) and 1 copy (7 pages); Print (and photocopy) United Music Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. Photocopy not signed. Photocopy from different printed score. (Box 33, Folder 0772)
  - Mortensen, Jørgen Organo. Movement VI, 1985, 1 score (9 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo organ Autograph reads, "August-September 1985. Vejrup, IX-30-1985. Jorgen Mortensen." Movement VI only. Pages 20-29. Titled Toccacatata. (Box 33, Folder 0773)
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 Adagio and Rondo, in C minor, K. 617, 1948, 1 score (16 pages) and 3 parts; Print International Music Company Instrumentation: For glass harmonica (or piano), flute, oboe, viola, and violoncello Missing viola part. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 33, Folder 0774)
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 Divertimento no. 7: in D major, K. 205, 195u, 1 score (18 pages); Print (miniature) E. Eulenburg Instrumentation: For violin, viola, bass, bassoon, and 2 horns (Box 33, Folder 0775)
  - Myhill, John, 1923-1987 Selections, undated, 1 score (22 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For voice and piano This appears to be two works: Light and dark for solo piano (2 copies) and a pair of songs with continuous pagination, pages 1-19. (Box 33, Folder 0776)
    Light and Dark -- I need your capital -- I had a little money [Lieder style].
  - Nancarrow, Conlon, 1912-1997 Study #3d for player piano, undated, 1 score (6 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: Originally for player piano, transcribed for solo piano This is Yvar Mikhashoff's transcription of the original player piano work for piano performer. Another copy can be found in his collection of transcriptions and arrangements. Additional name: Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993 (Box 33, Folder 0777)
  - Nancarrow, Conlon, 1912-1997 Study no. 15, undated, 1 score (5 pages); Computer-notated score Instrumentation: Originally for player piano, transcribed for solo piano This is Yvar Mikhashoff's transcription of the original player piano work for piano performer(s). The original manuscript copy of his transcription can be found in his collection of transcriptions and arrangements. Additional name: Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993 (Box 33, Folder 0778)
  - Nevin, Arthur, 1871-1943 Daughter of the forest: opening scene, 1918, 1 score (20 pages); Print (photocopy) J. Church Co. Instrumentation: Vocal score for voices and piano; originally for voices and orchestra Found in a folder labeled Around the World with American Opera. Text by Randolph Hartley. Additional name: Hartley, Randolph, 1870-1931 (Box 33, Folder 0779)
    First 20 pages of the opera.
  - Nono, Luigi ... sofferte onde serene …: for piano and magnetic tape, 1977, 1 score (14 pages); Print (reproduction of manuscript) Ricordi Instrumentation: For piano and tape Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 33, Folder 0780)
  - Oliveros, Pauline, 1932- Sonic Meditations, 1974, 1 score (8 pages); Print Smith Publications Instrumentation: Chance composition created by sounds produced during group meditations (Box 33, Folder 0781)
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1892-2002 Tarantelle, 1990, 1 score (12 pages); Print (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 33, Folder 0782)
  - Ornstein, Leo, 1892-2002 Three moods: anger, grief, joy, undated, 1 score (34 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 33, Folder 0783)
  - Palmer, Robert, 1915-2010 Toccata ostinato, 1945, 1 score (7 pages); Print Elkan-Vogel Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 33, Folder 0784)
  - Pantchev, Vladimir Nadsvirvne iz malka syuita, undated, 1 score (7 pages); Print Instrumentation: For solo piano Title transliterated from Cyrillic. Possible German title: Wettspiel (Box 33, Folder 0785)
  - Panni, Marcello Desire: Ragtime two step for piano, 1987, 1 score (9 pages); Print Edipan Instrumentation: For solo piano Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 33, Folder 0786)